bgov.com 2017-02-02

# Privacy Policy | Bloomberg Government

Bloomberg Finance L.P. and its operating agent Bloomberg L.P. (together, “the Bloomberg Group”) respect the privacy rights of our users and are strongly committed to protecting your privacy online. This privacy policy applies to information collected through the BLOOMBERG GOVERNMENTSM (BGOVSM) product web site (“this Site”) and does not apply to any other products or services or to information collected in any other way (whether offline or online), by the Bloomberg Group and its affiliates.

#### Information We Collect

The Bloomberg Group or a designated service provider collects information through this Site, such as during registration, when you request certain services or products, or submit information to enter a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion, or complete a survey or poll. This information includes personal information such as name, phone number, and e-mail address.

The Bloomberg Group or a designated service provider may use “cookies,” web server logs, web beacons, or other electronic tools to collect information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, language, operating system, computer platform, and the state or country from which you accessed this Site. The Bloomberg Group or a designated service provider may also use cookies, web server logs, web beacons, or other electronic tools to collect and compile statistical and other information about your use of this Site and the services provided on this Site, such as the web pages visited, the date and the time of your visit, the web sites you visited immediately before and after visiting this Site, the number of links you click within this Site, the functions you use on this Site, the databases you view and the searches you request on this Site, the data you save on or download from this Site, etc.

A cookie is a small text file placed on your computer. Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to disable cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. The help function on most browsers contains instructions on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies or to disable cookies entirely. However, note that this Site will not function properly if you disable cookies.

BACK TO TOP

#### How We Use and Disclose Your Information

The Bloomberg Group uses the information collected through this Site, including personal information and information about your use of this Site, to enhance your experience with this Site, save your preferences and login information, analyze web site usage, analyze use of the Site, communicate with you, enforce any terms of service or other agreement related to the Site, and provide you with services or products that you request. A portion of this Site is dedicated to a shared work space into which you may input your work product. The Bloomberg Group does not use or disclose any contents of the work product that you input into the shared work space on this Site except to third parties enabled by you and the Bloomberg Group on your behalf or to the third party that authorized you to use this Site. The Bloomberg Group may also use the information collected through this Site to provide special offers and promotions. You may instruct the Bloomberg Group at any time not to use your personal information collected through this Site to provide you with special offers and promotions by contacting [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com "email support@bgov.com"). You can also update your settings for receiving offers and promotions by email by [clicking here](http://www.bloomberg.com/email-settings/).

To assist us with the uses described in this privacy policy, information we or our designated service providers have collected about you through this Site, including your use of this Site, may be enhanced with other information about you that we have from other sources.

The Bloomberg Group may disclose your information to our affiliates, our service providers, and to the party who authorized your use of this Site, such as your employer. The Bloomberg Group may disclose to other third parties, including other users of this Site, information about your use of this Site and the services provided on this Site, but only in an aggregated and unattributed manner. The Bloomberg Group may also share your personal information collected through this Site with a sponsor or other third party (“Third-Party Providers”). You may instruct the Bloomberg Group at any time not to share your personal information with such Third Party Providers by contacting [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com).

The Bloomberg Group may also disclose your information to unaffiliated third parties if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary: (a) to comply with the law or in response to a subpoena, court order, government request, or other legal process; (b) to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of the Bloomberg Group or others; (c) to enforce any terms of service on this Site; (d) to provide you and the other users of this Site with the services or products requested by you and/or the other users (including allowing a purchaser of the Bloomberg Group to continue to serve you), and to perform other activities related to such services and products, including billing and collection; (e) to provide you with special offers or promotions from the Bloomberg Group to which you consented; and (f) to operate the Bloomberg Group’s systems properly.

BACK TO TOP

#### Accuracy and Security of Personal Information

Any of your personal information collected by the Bloomberg Group through this Site is kept on secure servers. The Bloomberg Group uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures to protect your personal information on such servers. To help us protect your privacy, you should maintain the secrecy of your username and password you set up in connection with your participation in this Site’s service.

BACK TO TOP

#### Public Records

Certain databases available to registered users of this Site may contain personal information received from third party data suppliers. This personal information is contained in public records, publicly available information, and non-public information (collectively, “public records information”). Your use of this information is restricted to specific, legitimate purposes, and such information may not be used to violate any applicable laws, rules, or regulations.

BACK TO TOP

#### Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information

To access, review, rectify, or delete personal information collected about you through this Site, please contact us at [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com) or please use your username and password to access the webpage on this Site designated for this purpose. All requests must include the following information: first name, last name, and e-mail address. While the Bloomberg Group will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request, we also reserve the right to impose certain restrictions and requirements on such access requests, if allowed or required by applicable laws.

If you wish to access, review, rectify, or delete personal information about you contained in public records information, you will need to contact the third-party supplier of the information directly. If you have any questions regarding public records information on this Site, please contact us at [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com).

BACK TO TOP

#### Transfer of Personal Information To Other Countries

Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this privacy policy may involve the transfer of your personal information to various countries around the world that may have different levels of privacy protection than your country. By submitting your personal information through this Site, you consent to such transfers.

BACK TO TOP

#### Links To Third-Party Web Sites

The Bloomberg Group may provide links to third-party web sites. Since we do not control third-party sites and are not responsible for any information you may provide while on such sites, we encourage you to read the privacy policies on those web sites before providing any of your information on such sites.

BACK TO TOP

#### Questions Regarding This Privacy Policy

If you have questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com).

BACK TO TOP

#### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by the Bloomberg Group to its affiliates and/or third parties for their direct marketing purposes.To make such a request, please send an email with your first name, last name, mailing address, email address and telephone number to [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com). Please include “California Privacy Rights” in the Subject line of your email. You may also make such a request by writing to us at:

Bloomberg L.P.  
Attn: Legal Department  
731 Lexington Avenue  
New York, NY 10022

BACK TO TOP

#### Modifications To This Privacy Policy

The Bloomberg Group reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time by posting revisions on this web page.

Such changes will be effective upon posting.
